wikidates.org 2017-06-30

# Cookie policy | WikiDates.org

To make this site work properly, we place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.

## What are cookies?

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.

## How do we use cookies?

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track how visitors use the Website. The resulting information, including the address of your computer (IP address) transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Please read the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/us/policies/technologies/ads/) for more information as well as the specific privacy policy of [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/us_ALL/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

Google uses this information to track how our website is used, to provide reports on the website to us and to provide its advertisers information about the effectiveness of their campaigns. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if Google is legally required, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. We have no influence on this matter.

### Facebook, Twitter and Google - Social media buttons

On this site buttons are included to promote pages or share on social networks Facebook, Twitter and Google. These buttons are implemented by code provided by Facebook, Twitter and Google itself. This code places a cookie (see above).

Please read the privacy policy of [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php), [Twitter](https://twitter.com/privacy) and [Google](http://www.google.com/intl/uk/policies/technologies/ads/) (which can change frequently) to see what they do with your personal data.

### Ad networks

Also, any external advertising network (including Google Adsense and / or Criteo) on this website uses technologies such as cookies and web beacons to display relevant ads to you during your visit to this website. This information (it is NOT your name, address, email address or phone number) can be used to show relevant ads on other websites.

We don't have access to the cookies and web beacons sent by ad networks.

For more information about the Google Adsense Privacy Policy, please consult the privacy policy of this service (see above). We have no influence or control over the privacy practices of ad networks like Google Adsense.

You have the right to request access to and correction or deletion of your data. Please see our contact page. To prevent abuse, we may ask you to identify adequately. When it comes to access personal data linked to a cookie, you must send a copy of the cookie in question.

Cookies can be deleted only by yourself, since they are stored on your computer. Consult the manual of your browser.

Some tracking cookies are placed by third parties that display including through our website ads to you.

Through our website, a cookie is placed from the US company Google, as part of the "Analytics" service. We use this service to track and get reports about how visitors use the website. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if Google is legally required, or if third parties process the information on Google's behalf. We have no influence on this matter.

The information that Google collects is anonymous as much as possible. The information is transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.

## How you can control advertising cookies?

You can use [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/?hl=us) to manage the Google ads you see and opt out of interest-based ads. Even if you opt out of interest-based ads, you may still see ads based on factors such as your general location derived from your IP address, your browser type and recent, previous searches related to your current search.

You can also manage many companies’ cookies used for online advertising at the US-based [aboutads.info choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) page or the EU-based [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Finally, you can [manage cookies in your web browser](http://www.google.com/intl/us/policies/technologies/managing/).
